Guide to the Franklin and Bertha Schweinfurth Ohlinger Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1868-1972, n.d.; Series V
  - Biographical documentation
    - FO: Chinese calling cards, invitations to ceremonies, etc., ca. 1900-1912 (Box 14, Folder 243)
    - BSO: Biographical documents inc. school report and award cards, excerpts from diary, programs from meetings at which BSO spoke, 1868-1903 (Box 12, Folder 223)
    - BSO: Biographical documents inc. re. family history and her funeral service, 1923-1934 (Box 12, Folder 224)
    - BSO: Notes, inc.on books read, Bible study, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - FO BSO: Small volume Shakespeare that contains FO's penciled message to family, written in time of danger in Korea; Birthday book, 1886, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - Listing of Ohlinger material donated to Rutherford B. Hayes Library, Fremont, OH (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Artifacts
    - 2 Chinese shoes for bound feet; 1 pair small Chinese slippers (Box 12, Folder 228)